[Music]
Welcome to business central launch event
2025 release day one. In this session we
will show you new connectors related to
e documents. So we are doing we are
adding new connectors and we want to
have as more connectors as possible for
you. So you can choose which one to use.
We do not want to be dependent on one or
two. So we want to have more options for
you. So we are planning to add more
global available connectors. I put
accent on globals because for local
connectors the only opportunity is to
have them on app source by local
providers. Okay let's look what we had
before 2025 release one. So with
previous uh release we had two
connectors. We started with pag and
after that we added avalara. So we had
we have and we had these two connectors.
But now with uh 2025 release v1 we added
two more connectors. So now we have
logic and sign up or xflow. Uh probably
this is much more famous xflow. They're
available from 26.0. So from April
release they will be in public preview
for 1 month and from 26.1 they will be
in general
availability. This is what we have in
this moment. But there is more to come.
We are currently close to finish code
review. So probably 26.2 we will have
continue connector. After that we will
continue with for now and few more
connectors. So we will have more
connectors in a bus central in next few
minors. Idea as I said is to have more
connectors but we need to be very
careful how we will proceed with that.
So now how you can find these
connectors. These connectors are already
on available on apps source. So you can
go on apps source you can find e
document monitor for signup and logic
without any problem and as I mentioned
uh next continue will be in 26.2 but
probably we will publish on app source
maybe even a little bit earlier because
publish on app source is not dependent
on our uh versions. So we are trying to
do to make this as soon as possible for
you and you can choose what what one you
want to use. But what is now important
uh you can choose you can set up all
these connector directly from a busy
central. Now we changed a little bit uh
approach how you can choose how you can
set up them directly but now I have my
colleague Magnus and he will show
exactly how you can set up what you need
to do and how you can enable especially
with the focus to two new connectors.
Thank you, Alexander. Let's uh let's see
how we do that in the product. So, uh
before this release, we uh used to
pre-install our first party uh
connectors, but uh with the feedback
we've gotten from the community and our
partners, we have changed this model in
this release to now releasing them uh on
AppSource and making it very easy in the
product, which I will demonstrate now
how you can go and install them uh from
there. So here is a business central
tenant and all you have to do is just go
to e document
services open that list page and from
here under related you can see the new
action install e document integrations
from appsource so we'll click that and
this will open up the appsource
marketplace inside business central and
here we can see a list of Microsoft
published applications that are related
to e documents. So we have a set of
connectors. We can see Avalara is here.
We can see Logic and Signup, the two new
ones that we are super excited to have
in the product. And then of course we
also have local formats here that you
can choose uh to install if needed. So
it's actually very simple, very
straightforward. I will take Logic as an
example. I already installed signup. So
let's open up Logic. And here you can
read a bit about the connector in the
description. And you can click install
app.
And then we just install it in English
language, but that is fine. And that
should only take a few seconds. Reload
the
environment and your app is installed
and ready to
use. So with that installed, all you now
need to do is again open up e document
services. From here, create a new one or
go to an existing one. I'll use the the
demo service we have. And then in the
service integration we can now see that
logic is also available since we have
installed it. So I can pick that one and
then just like any other connector that
we've had from from Avalar Pagarero, you
always go to the setup service
integration and this will open up the
the card page where you will go and fill
in the information and details needed to
actually
integration with the for instance the
logic uh service in this case. And
that's it. Uh very straightforward, very
simple. A few clicks in the product and
you are up and running.
So that's all. Thank you Magnus. And
what is extremely important this is the
last step what Magnus show all
connectors never mind which one you will
use they have absolutely the same user
experience. So even if you use in one
country for example one company one
connector and when you switch to another
connector this is again the same. You
just need to choose which one you want
to use and to use the same action for
setting up and that's it. This is
everything. This is what we wanted to
achieve to have absolutely the same user
experience when you're using e
documents. Only difference is if you
have different uh uh connector so you
need to have contact with these
providers but in general user experience
in B central is absolutely the same. So
now I would like to invite you to watch
more videos related to electronic
documents because we have six different
videos this release. We deliver so many
different features related to electronic
documents in this wave. So I inviting
you again please find these videos and
watch them. And now in both Magus my
name thank you for watching this video.